[
  {
    "question": "My mother is ... economist",
    "choice1": "the",
    "choice2": "an",
    "choice3": "a",
    "choice4": "-",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "I have bought three (dozen) tickets to the cinema today.    ",
    "choice1": "dozenes",
    "choice2": "dozens",
    "choice3": "dozenos",
    "choice4": "dozen",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "My son ... like geometry",
    "choice1": "do not",
    "choice2": "does not",
    "choice3": "not",
    "choice4": "is not",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "I ... to school every day",
    "choice1": "goes",
    "choice2": "am",
    "choice3": "went",
    "choice4": "go",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "John bought ... cap",
    "choice1": "a",
    "choice2": "the",
    "choice3": "an",
    "choice4": "-",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "They ... at work now",
    "choice1": "are",
    "choice2": "be",
    "choice3": "is",
    "choice4": "am",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "I love Russia. ... am in St. Petersburg now",
    "choice1": "He",
    "choice2": "She",
    "choice3": "I",
    "choice4": "me",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you got a ball? Yes, I ... .",
    "choice1": "have",
    "choice2": "do",
    "choice3": "am",
    "choice4": "ball",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you got many violets in your ...?",
    "choice1": "office",
    "choice2": "school",
    "choice3": "garden",
    "choice4": "store",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Is ... a zebra or tiger?",
    "choice1": "these",
    "choice2": "this",
    "choice3": "their",
    "choice4": "their",
    "answer": 2
  }
]